{
    "subject": "resource/TransAdelaide",
    "predicate": "property/preceding",
    "object": "resource/State_Transport_Authority_(South_Australia)",
    "human_readable": "TransAdelaide was preceded by State Transport Authority (South Australia).",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9661319851875305,
            "question": "Which public transport authority existed in South Australia prior to TransAdelaide?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9469194412231445,
            "question": "What was the name of the organization that preceded TransAdelaide in South Australia?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9392558932304382,
            "question": "Is there a historical record of the transition from State Transport Authority (South Australia) to TransAdelaide?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8858784437179565,
            "question": "Were there any public concerns or debates surrounding the replacement of State Transport Authority (South Australia) with TransAdelaide?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8781524896621704,
            "question": "What changes occurred when TransAdelaide replaced State Transport Authority (South Australia)?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8273375034332275,
            "question": "What is the full name of the organization that preceded TransAdelaide?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8104727268218994,
            "question": "What are some key differences between State Transport Authority (South Australia) and TransAdelaide?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6637336015701294,
            "question": "How was TransAdelaide formed?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6557443141937256,
            "question": "When did State Transport Authority (South Australia) cease to exist?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6225326061248779,
            "question": "What organization came before TransAdelaide?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=TransAdelaide was preceded by State Transport Authority (South Australia).",
            "html": "dbpedia_6462_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=When did State Transport Authority (South Australia) cease to exist?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6462_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How was TransAdelaide formed?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6462_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some key differences between State Transport Authority (South Australia) and TransAdelaide?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6462_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6462_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6462_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6462_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6462_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6462_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6462_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6462_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6462_34.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6462_8.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6462_9.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\nLet me know if you'd like to evaluate more triples!"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe context information clearly indicates that the State Transport Authority (STA) of South Australia was dissolved and reformed into TransAdelaide in 1994, as a prelude to competitive tendering for public transport services. This supports the statement that TransAdelaide was preceded by the State Transport Authority (South Australia)."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}